http://molecularstation.com/privacy-policy/

Member Login
Remember me
Lost Password?
Privacy Policy - Molecular Station
Molecular Station understands your privacy and will not sell or give this information to outside sources.
Molecular Station collects personal information about you only when you
specifically and knowingly provide it to us, such as forum and blog registration purposes.
This personal information that you provide to Molecular Station will not be
made available to third parties outside of Molecular Station without your
explicit permission. Your personal information will
be used to personalize and enhance your experience with Molecular Station.
The Use of Cookies
Cookies are data which a web site transfers to an individual's
hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can enhance the web by making it more useful by
storing
your preferences for a particular site. The use of
cookies is an internet and industry standard, and many if not most major web sites use them to provide
enhanced features for their users.
Molecular Station
has two primary uses for its cookies. We use them primarily
to specify your unique preferences, and to make it easier for you to use our forum and other registration areas. Secondly, we use cookies to track user trends and
patterns on Molecular Station. This enables us to better understand and improve areas of Molecular Station Service. While these activities depend on
the use of a "cookie," visitors to Molecular Station always have the
option of disabling cookies through their internet browser preferences or options.  Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You either can reset your
browser to refuse all cookies, or indicate when a cookie is being sent, or block cookies from Molecular Station.
However, some Molecular Station Services such as our forum may not function
properly if you refuse cookies.
External Links and Links to other Sites and Servers
Molecular Station contains many links
to other sites. Those sites may not have the same privacy standards as
Molecular Station. These sites may send their own cookies to users, and
consequently collect personal information and data that Molecular Station would
not.
Users should be aware that when you are on Molecular Station, you could be
directed to other sites that are beyond our control. There are links to other
sites from Molecular Station pages that take you outside our service. These other
sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data or solicit personal
information. Take note and caution when proceeding to other sites.
Molecular Station's
policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the
operation of the Internet, and therefore beyond Molecular Station's control, and
is not to be applied in any manner contrary to applicable law or governmental
regulation.
2005-2012 Molecular Station. All rights reserved.
Recommended Links
Los Angeles Personal Injury Attorney
Personal Injury Attorney Encino
